{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912487107","data":{"timestamp":" 946912487107"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" c3f3d489-9de9-4096-808b-8704f1dbc9d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_mwu-ta-shi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912492598","data":{"timestamp":" 946912492598"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" c3f3d489-9de9-4096-808b-8704f1dbc9d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ng'i-ta-mwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912499809","data":{"timestamp":" 946912499809"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" c3f3d489-9de9-4096-808b-8704f1dbc9d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ti-ta-mwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912505138","data":{"timestamp":" 946912505138"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" c3f3d489-9de9-4096-808b-8704f1dbc9d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ku-ta-nyi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912511543","data":{"timestamp":" 946912511543"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" c3f3d489-9de9-4096-808b-8704f1dbc9d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-vyi-ve"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912520100","data":{"timestamp":" 946912520099"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" c3f3d489-9de9-4096-808b-8704f1dbc9d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-pe-ngu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912533683","data":{"timestamp":" 946912533683"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" c3f3d489-9de9-4096-808b-8704f1dbc9d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_mche-ta-mpi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912538812","data":{"timestamp":" 946912538812"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" c3f3d489-9de9-4096-808b-8704f1dbc9d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_do-ta-mo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912544916","data":{"timestamp":" 946912544916"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" c3f3d489-9de9-4096-808b-8704f1dbc9d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ng'u-fo-ta"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912555112","data":{"timestamp":" 946912555112"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" c3f3d489-9de9-4096-808b-8704f1dbc9d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_si-ta-shu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912560187","data":{"timestamp":" 946912560187"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" c3f3d489-9de9-4096-808b-8704f1dbc9d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_si-ta-shu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912568815","data":{"timestamp":" 946912568815"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" c3f3d489-9de9-4096-808b-8704f1dbc9d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_si-ta-shu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912578540","data":{"timestamp":" 946912578539"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" c3f3d489-9de9-4096-808b-8704f1dbc9d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_si-ta-shu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912594052","data":{"timestamp":" 946912594052"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 67a944d4-9d8c-40ad-86d0-f81d4072eb7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912603449","data":{"timestamp":" 946912603449"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 67a944d4-9d8c-40ad-86d0-f81d4072eb7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912613529","data":{"timestamp":" 946912613529"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 67a944d4-9d8c-40ad-86d0-f81d4072eb7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912623941","data":{"timestamp":" 946912623941"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 67a944d4-9d8c-40ad-86d0-f81d4072eb7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912632184","data":{"timestamp":" 946912632184"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 67a944d4-9d8c-40ad-86d0-f81d4072eb7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912640939","data":{"timestamp":" 946912640939"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 67a944d4-9d8c-40ad-86d0-f81d4072eb7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912648794","data":{"timestamp":" 946912648794"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 67a944d4-9d8c-40ad-86d0-f81d4072eb7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912657310","data":{"timestamp":" 946912657310"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 67a944d4-9d8c-40ad-86d0-f81d4072eb7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912668091","data":{"timestamp":" 946912668091"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 67a944d4-9d8c-40ad-86d0-f81d4072eb7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912676779","data":{"timestamp":" 946912676779"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 67a944d4-9d8c-40ad-86d0-f81d4072eb7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912685098","data":{"timestamp":" 946912685098"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 67a944d4-9d8c-40ad-86d0-f81d4072eb7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946912696315","data":{"timestamp":" 946912696315"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 67a944d4-9d8c-40ad-86d0-f81d4072eb7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945820431","data":{"timestamp":" 946945820431"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 8a31497a-631e-44a0-a7d8-e7eb1d9d43dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945829926","data":{"timestamp":" 946945829925"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 8a31497a-631e-44a0-a7d8-e7eb1d9d43dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945836893","data":{"timestamp":" 946945836892"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 8a31497a-631e-44a0-a7d8-e7eb1d9d43dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945846539","data":{"timestamp":" 946945846539"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 8a31497a-631e-44a0-a7d8-e7eb1d9d43dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945856050","data":{"timestamp":" 946945856050"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 8a31497a-631e-44a0-a7d8-e7eb1d9d43dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945864230","data":{"timestamp":" 946945864230"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 8a31497a-631e-44a0-a7d8-e7eb1d9d43dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945874862","data":{"timestamp":" 946945874862"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 8a31497a-631e-44a0-a7d8-e7eb1d9d43dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945884964","data":{"timestamp":" 946945884963"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 8a31497a-631e-44a0-a7d8-e7eb1d9d43dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945893103","data":{"timestamp":" 946945893103"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 8a31497a-631e-44a0-a7d8-e7eb1d9d43dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945902314","data":{"timestamp":" 946945902314"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 8a31497a-631e-44a0-a7d8-e7eb1d9d43dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945909485","data":{"timestamp":" 946945909485"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 8a31497a-631e-44a0-a7d8-e7eb1d9d43dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945925112","data":{"timestamp":" 946945925112"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 8a31497a-631e-44a0-a7d8-e7eb1d9d43dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945930627","data":{"timestamp":" 946945930627"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 8a31497a-631e-44a0-a7d8-e7eb1d9d43dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945937642","data":{"timestamp":" 946945937642"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 8a31497a-631e-44a0-a7d8-e7eb1d9d43dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945945808","data":{"timestamp":" 946945945808"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 8a31497a-631e-44a0-a7d8-e7eb1d9d43dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945996826","data":{"timestamp":" 946945996826"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 8a31497a-631e-44a0-a7d8-e7eb1d9d43dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946022365","data":{"timestamp":" 946946022364"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7f2e4170-7830-43ea-9aa6-2167dfe36ce5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_de_cha_ta"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946029013","data":{"timestamp":" 946946029013"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7f2e4170-7830-43ea-9aa6-2167dfe36ce5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ta_ndi_nyu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946035711","data":{"timestamp":" 946946035710"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7f2e4170-7830-43ea-9aa6-2167dfe36ce5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pa_ta_nji"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946042365","data":{"timestamp":" 946946042365"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7f2e4170-7830-43ea-9aa6-2167dfe36ce5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nya_thi_ta"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946049027","data":{"timestamp":" 946946049027"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7f2e4170-7830-43ea-9aa6-2167dfe36ce5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_to_ta_nje"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946055679","data":{"timestamp":" 946946055679"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7f2e4170-7830-43ea-9aa6-2167dfe36ce5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_za_ta_fa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946062350","data":{"timestamp":" 946946062350"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7f2e4170-7830-43ea-9aa6-2167dfe36ce5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vyu_ta_ru"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946068980","data":{"timestamp":" 946946068979"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7f2e4170-7830-43ea-9aa6-2167dfe36ce5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fa_ta_yi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946075631","data":{"timestamp":" 946946075631"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7f2e4170-7830-43ea-9aa6-2167dfe36ce5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ka_ta_mto"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946082277","data":{"timestamp":" 946946082276"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7f2e4170-7830-43ea-9aa6-2167dfe36ce5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mi_ta_nga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946095335","data":{"timestamp":" 946946095334"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7f2e4170-7830-43ea-9aa6-2167dfe36ce5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ta..ta.noShow..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_mi_ta_nga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946135803","data":{"timestamp":" 946946135803"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946136592","data":{"timestamp":" 946946136592"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946137673","data":{"timestamp":" 946946137672"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOAMKA"," userResponse":" NILIPOAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946138819","data":{"timestamp":" 946946138818"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPATA"," userResponse":" NILIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946139497","data":{"timestamp":" 946946139497"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIAMSHA"," userResponse":" KIAMSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946139999","data":{"timestamp":" 946946139999"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWA"," userResponse":" KINYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946140565","data":{"timestamp":" 946946140564"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946140818","data":{"timestamp":" 946946140818"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946141575","data":{"timestamp":" 946946141575"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946145481","data":{"timestamp":" 946946145481"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikimbia kwenda kukutana na rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" NILIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946145907","data":{"timestamp":" 946946145907"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikimbia kwenda kukutana na rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946146754","data":{"timestamp":" 946946146754"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikimbia kwenda kukutana na rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUTANA"," userResponse":" KUKUTANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946146958","data":{"timestamp":" 946946146957"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikimbia kwenda kukutana na rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946147630","data":{"timestamp":" 946946147629"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikimbia kwenda kukutana na rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946147986","data":{"timestamp":" 946946147986"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikimbia kwenda kukutana na rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946148686","data":{"timestamp":" 946946148685"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikimbia kwenda kukutana na rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946151837","data":{"timestamp":" 946946151836"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pindi nilipompata Muthoni tulisahau kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINDI"," userResponse":" PINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946152843","data":{"timestamp":" 946946152843"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pindi nilipompata Muthoni tulisahau kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOMPATA"," userResponse":" NILIPOMPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946153871","data":{"timestamp":" 946946153870"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pindi nilipompata Muthoni tulisahau kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946155038","data":{"timestamp":" 946946155038"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pindi nilipompata Muthoni tulisahau kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISAHAU"," userResponse":" TULISAHAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946155873","data":{"timestamp":" 946946155873"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pindi nilipompata Muthoni tulisahau kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946156264","data":{"timestamp":" 946946156264"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pindi nilipompata Muthoni tulisahau kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946159253","data":{"timestamp":" 946946159253"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946159442","data":{"timestamp":" 946946159441"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946160253","data":{"timestamp":" 946946160253"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946161368","data":{"timestamp":" 946946161367"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULICHEZA"," userResponse":" TULICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946162073","data":{"timestamp":" 946946162073"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MICHEZO"," userResponse":" MICHEZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946162907","data":{"timestamp":" 946946162907"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946163485","data":{"timestamp":" 946946163484"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946163632","data":{"timestamp":" 946946163632"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946164160","data":{"timestamp":" 946946164160"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946167018","data":{"timestamp":" 946946167017"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulifanya kila kitu pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946167202","data":{"timestamp":" 946946167202"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulifanya kila kitu pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946167817","data":{"timestamp":" 946946167817"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulifanya kila kitu pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946168572","data":{"timestamp":" 946946168570"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulifanya kila kitu pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFANYA"," userResponse":" TULIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946169181","data":{"timestamp":" 946946169181"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulifanya kila kitu pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946169579","data":{"timestamp":" 946946169578"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulifanya kila kitu pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946170285","data":{"timestamp":" 946946170282"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulifanya kila kitu pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946174205","data":{"timestamp":" 946946174205"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIAHIDIANA"," userResponse":" TULIAHIDIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946174927","data":{"timestamp":" 946946174927"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946175659","data":{"timestamp":" 946946175658"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDII"," userResponse":" BIDII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946176221","data":{"timestamp":" 946946176221"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946176907","data":{"timestamp":" 946946176907"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946177490","data":{"timestamp":" 946946177490"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946178054","data":{"timestamp":" 946946178054"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946178790","data":{"timestamp":" 946946178790"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFUZU"," userResponse":" KUFUZU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946179316","data":{"timestamp":" 946946179316"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYEMA"," userResponse":" VYEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946182284","data":{"timestamp":" 946946182284"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini siku moja Muthoni hakufika shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946182708","data":{"timestamp":" 946946182708"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini siku moja Muthoni hakufika shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946183293","data":{"timestamp":" 946946183293"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini siku moja Muthoni hakufika shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946184106","data":{"timestamp":" 946946184106"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini siku moja Muthoni hakufika shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946184946","data":{"timestamp":" 946946184946"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini siku moja Muthoni hakufika shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUFIKA"," userResponse":" HAKUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946185779","data":{"timestamp":" 946946185779"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini siku moja Muthoni hakufika shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946188642","data":{"timestamp":" 946946188641"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisimama mlangoni nikimsubiri lakini hakufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISIMAMA"," userResponse":" NILISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946189616","data":{"timestamp":" 946946189616"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisimama mlangoni nikimsubiri lakini hakufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGONI"," userResponse":" MLANGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946190875","data":{"timestamp":" 946946190875"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisimama mlangoni nikimsubiri lakini hakufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIMSUBIRI"," userResponse":" NIKIMSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946192130","data":{"timestamp":" 946946192130"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisimama mlangoni nikimsubiri lakini hakufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946193378","data":{"timestamp":" 946946193378"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisimama mlangoni nikimsubiri lakini hakufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUFIKA"," userResponse":" HAKUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946196603","data":{"timestamp":" 946946196603"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946197036","data":{"timestamp":" 946946197035"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946198036","data":{"timestamp":" 946946198036"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPORUDI"," userResponse":" NILIPORUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946198900","data":{"timestamp":" 946946198899"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946200124","data":{"timestamp":" 946946200124"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" NILIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946200544","data":{"timestamp":" 946946200544"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946201218","data":{"timestamp":" 946946201218"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946202045","data":{"timestamp":" 946946202045"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946202828","data":{"timestamp":" 946946202828"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUFIKA"," userResponse":" HAKUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946203445","data":{"timestamp":" 946946203444"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946203886","data":{"timestamp":" 946946203886"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946204285","data":{"timestamp":" 946946204285"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946207842","data":{"timestamp":" 946946207842"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliendelea na masomo yangu lakini nilimkosa Muthoni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIENDELEA"," userResponse":" NILIENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946208035","data":{"timestamp":" 946946208035"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliendelea na masomo yangu lakini nilimkosa Muthoni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946208733","data":{"timestamp":" 946946208729"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliendelea na masomo yangu lakini nilimkosa Muthoni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946209187","data":{"timestamp":" 946946209186"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliendelea na masomo yangu lakini nilimkosa Muthoni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946210158","data":{"timestamp":" 946946210158"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliendelea na masomo yangu lakini nilimkosa Muthoni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946211077","data":{"timestamp":" 946946211077"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliendelea na masomo yangu lakini nilimkosa Muthoni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMKOSA"," userResponse":" NILIMKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946211763","data":{"timestamp":" 946946211763"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliendelea na masomo yangu lakini nilimkosa Muthoni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946212672","data":{"timestamp":" 946946212671"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliendelea na masomo yangu lakini nilimkosa Muthoni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946215407","data":{"timestamp":" 946946215407"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila nilipoenda shuleni nilimtafuta Muthoni kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946216322","data":{"timestamp":" 946946216322"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila nilipoenda shuleni nilimtafuta Muthoni kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOENDA"," userResponse":" NILIPOENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946217206","data":{"timestamp":" 946946217206"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila nilipoenda shuleni nilimtafuta Muthoni kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946218592","data":{"timestamp":" 946946218591"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila nilipoenda shuleni nilimtafuta Muthoni kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMTAFUTA"," userResponse":" NILIMTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946219224","data":{"timestamp":" 946946219224"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila nilipoenda shuleni nilimtafuta Muthoni kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946219861","data":{"timestamp":" 946946219861"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila nilipoenda shuleni nilimtafuta Muthoni kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946220546","data":{"timestamp":" 946946220546"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila nilipoenda shuleni nilimtafuta Muthoni kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946223709","data":{"timestamp":" 946946223708"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946224469","data":{"timestamp":" 946946224469"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEKUWA"," userResponse":" NIMEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946225105","data":{"timestamp":" 946946225105"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946225776","data":{"timestamp":" 946946225776"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946226857","data":{"timestamp":" 946946226856"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946227750","data":{"timestamp":" 946946227749"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMKOSA"," userResponse":" NINAMKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946228494","data":{"timestamp":" 946946228494"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946228854","data":{"timestamp":" 946946228853"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946229575","data":{"timestamp":" 946946229575"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946232434","data":{"timestamp":" 946946232433"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946232543","data":{"timestamp":" 946946232543"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946239477","data":{"timestamp":" 946946239476"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" b4cd860a-df6f-4a64-8a90-9f939a7de45f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946254861","data":{"timestamp":" 946946254861"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" af241600-2585-40ea-83d4-d13b15a1de0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_je-ta-do"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946260374","data":{"timestamp":" 946946260374"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" af241600-2585-40ea-83d4-d13b15a1de0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-mcho-bo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946265079","data":{"timestamp":" 946946265079"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" af241600-2585-40ea-83d4-d13b15a1de0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_mre-ma-ta"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946269796","data":{"timestamp":" 946946269795"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" af241600-2585-40ea-83d4-d13b15a1de0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-mwu-vyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946276250","data":{"timestamp":" 946946276249"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" af241600-2585-40ea-83d4-d13b15a1de0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_bu-ta-mte"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946281352","data":{"timestamp":" 946946281352"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" af241600-2585-40ea-83d4-d13b15a1de0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_mre-cha-ta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946289326","data":{"timestamp":" 946946289325"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" af241600-2585-40ea-83d4-d13b15a1de0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-mla-nya"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946294934","data":{"timestamp":" 946946294934"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" af241600-2585-40ea-83d4-d13b15a1de0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_pi-be-ta"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946300286","data":{"timestamp":" 946946300285"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" af241600-2585-40ea-83d4-d13b15a1de0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_pe-ta-mju"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946304563","data":{"timestamp":" 946946304563"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" af241600-2585-40ea-83d4-d13b15a1de0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_pa-ta-dha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946310376","data":{"timestamp":" 946946310375"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" af241600-2585-40ea-83d4-d13b15a1de0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_pa-ta-dha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946324888","data":{"timestamp":" 946946324888"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7150b98c-3b51-4cd2-ba8c-5b82adaa8341"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946329944","data":{"timestamp":" 946946329944"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7150b98c-3b51-4cd2-ba8c-5b82adaa8341"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946334493","data":{"timestamp":" 946946334493"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7150b98c-3b51-4cd2-ba8c-5b82adaa8341"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946342607","data":{"timestamp":" 946946342607"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7150b98c-3b51-4cd2-ba8c-5b82adaa8341"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946351931","data":{"timestamp":" 946946351930"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7150b98c-3b51-4cd2-ba8c-5b82adaa8341"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946357769","data":{"timestamp":" 946946357768"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7150b98c-3b51-4cd2-ba8c-5b82adaa8341"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946363849","data":{"timestamp":" 946946363849"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7150b98c-3b51-4cd2-ba8c-5b82adaa8341"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946368342","data":{"timestamp":" 946946368342"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7150b98c-3b51-4cd2-ba8c-5b82adaa8341"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946373011","data":{"timestamp":" 946946373010"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7150b98c-3b51-4cd2-ba8c-5b82adaa8341"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946377819","data":{"timestamp":" 946946377819"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7150b98c-3b51-4cd2-ba8c-5b82adaa8341"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946386219","data":{"timestamp":" 946946386219"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7150b98c-3b51-4cd2-ba8c-5b82adaa8341"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946392898","data":{"timestamp":" 946946392897"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 7150b98c-3b51-4cd2-ba8c-5b82adaa8341"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946403465","data":{"timestamp":" 946946403465"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 124aad53-021f-4e0e-9151-d2bc85221997"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946404501","data":{"timestamp":" 946946404500"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 124aad53-021f-4e0e-9151-d2bc85221997"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TA"," userResponse":" TA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946407288","data":{"timestamp":" 946946407288"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 124aad53-021f-4e0e-9151-d2bc85221997"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" te"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946408336","data":{"timestamp":" 946946408336"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 124aad53-021f-4e0e-9151-d2bc85221997"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" te"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TE"," userResponse":" TE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946411571","data":{"timestamp":" 946946411571"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 124aad53-021f-4e0e-9151-d2bc85221997"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946412613","data":{"timestamp":" 946946412613"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 124aad53-021f-4e0e-9151-d2bc85221997"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TI"," userResponse":" TI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946415543","data":{"timestamp":" 946946415543"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 124aad53-021f-4e0e-9151-d2bc85221997"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" to"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946416588","data":{"timestamp":" 946946416588"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 124aad53-021f-4e0e-9151-d2bc85221997"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" to"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TO"," userResponse":" TO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946419200","data":{"timestamp":" 946946419200"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 124aad53-021f-4e0e-9151-d2bc85221997"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946420231","data":{"timestamp":" 946946420231"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 124aad53-021f-4e0e-9151-d2bc85221997"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946423494","data":{"timestamp":" 946946423494"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 124aad53-021f-4e0e-9151-d2bc85221997"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" tu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946423660","data":{"timestamp":" 946946423660"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 124aad53-021f-4e0e-9151-d2bc85221997"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946446765","data":{"timestamp":" 946946446765"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946447381","data":{"timestamp":" 946946447381"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946447597","data":{"timestamp":" 946946447597"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946448280","data":{"timestamp":" 946946448280"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABASI"," userResponse":" MABASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946449034","data":{"timestamp":" 946946449034"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946449549","data":{"timestamp":" 946946449549"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWETU"," userResponse":" MWETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946450644","data":{"timestamp":" 946946450644"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIJAA"," userResponse":" KILIJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946451575","data":{"timestamp":" 946946451575"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" SHUGHULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946451959","data":{"timestamp":" 946946451959"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946452404","data":{"timestamp":" 946946452404"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946452610","data":{"timestamp":" 946946452610"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946453329","data":{"timestamp":" 946946453329"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABASI"," userResponse":" MABASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946455691","data":{"timestamp":" 946946455691"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946456126","data":{"timestamp":" 946946456126"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946456904","data":{"timestamp":" 946946456904"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946457799","data":{"timestamp":" 946946457799"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIMEJAZA"," userResponse":" ZIMEJAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946458643","data":{"timestamp":" 946946458643"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946461090","data":{"timestamp":" 946946461090"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946461905","data":{"timestamp":" 946946461904"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946462129","data":{"timestamp":" 946946462129"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946462814","data":{"timestamp":" 946946462813"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946463501","data":{"timestamp":" 946946463500"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946463596","data":{"timestamp":" 946946463596"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946464402","data":{"timestamp":" 946946464401"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPAKIA"," userResponse":" KUPAKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946467175","data":{"timestamp":" 946946467175"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" KONDAKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946468091","data":{"timestamp":" 946946468091"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIITA"," userResponse":" WALIITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946468825","data":{"timestamp":" 946946468825"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJINA"," userResponse":" MAJINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946469839","data":{"timestamp":" 946946469839"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946469953","data":{"timestamp":" 946946469953"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946470736","data":{"timestamp":" 946946470736"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946471450","data":{"timestamp":" 946946471450"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946472650","data":{"timestamp":" 946946472650"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIELEKEA"," userResponse":" ZILIELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946475931","data":{"timestamp":" 946946475931"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946478667","data":{"timestamp":" 946946478667"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946480973","data":{"timestamp":" 946946480973"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946483662","data":{"timestamp":" 946946483661"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGHARIBI"," userResponse":" MAGHARIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946485734","data":{"timestamp":" 946946485734"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISIKIA"," userResponse":" NILISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946486520","data":{"timestamp":" 946946486520"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" KONDAKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946487305","data":{"timestamp":" 946946487305"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIITA"," userResponse":" AKIITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946487555","data":{"timestamp":" 946946487554"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946488170","data":{"timestamp":" 946946488169"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946490620","data":{"timestamp":" 946946490620"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946491084","data":{"timestamp":" 946946491084"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946491571","data":{"timestamp":" 946946491571"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946492684","data":{"timestamp":" 946946492684"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIYOHITAJI"," userResponse":" NILIYOHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946493510","data":{"timestamp":" 946946493510"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946494035","data":{"timestamp":" 946946494035"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946494740","data":{"timestamp":" 946946494740"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USAFIRI"," userResponse":" USAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946495214","data":{"timestamp":" 946946495214"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946497937","data":{"timestamp":" 946946497936"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946498108","data":{"timestamp":" 946946498108"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946498606","data":{"timestamp":" 946946498606"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946499283","data":{"timestamp":" 946946499283"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" JIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946499937","data":{"timestamp":" 946946499937"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946500598","data":{"timestamp":" 946946500598"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946501209","data":{"timestamp":" 946946501209"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJAA"," userResponse":" KUJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946502037","data":{"timestamp":" 946946502037"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946502438","data":{"timestamp":" 946946502437"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946503223","data":{"timestamp":" 946946503222"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946504958","data":{"timestamp":" 946946504958"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIJISHUGHULISHA"," userResponse":" WALIJISHUGHULISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946505755","data":{"timestamp":" 946946505755"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAKA"," userResponse":" KUTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946506450","data":{"timestamp":" 946946506450"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946509021","data":{"timestamp":" 946946509020"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946509397","data":{"timestamp":" 946946509396"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946510421","data":{"timestamp":" 946946510421"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPAKIA"," userResponse":" WALIPAKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946511286","data":{"timestamp":" 946946511286"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946511992","data":{"timestamp":" 946946511992"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946512137","data":{"timestamp":" 946946512136"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946512636","data":{"timestamp":" 946946512636"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946515073","data":{"timestamp":" 946946515073"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946516100","data":{"timestamp":" 946946516100"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIWEKA"," userResponse":" WALIIWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946516663","data":{"timestamp":" 946946516663"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946517409","data":{"timestamp":" 946946517409"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946517532","data":{"timestamp":" 946946517532"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946517887","data":{"timestamp":" 946946517886"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946521172","data":{"timestamp":" 946946521172"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946521748","data":{"timestamp":" 946946521748"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPYA"," userResponse":" WAPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946522516","data":{"timestamp":" 946946522515"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISHIKA"," userResponse":" WALISHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946523032","data":{"timestamp":" 946946523032"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKETI"," userResponse":" TIKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946523693","data":{"timestamp":" 946946523692"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946524406","data":{"timestamp":" 946946524405"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946525383","data":{"timestamp":" 946946525381"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" WAKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946525948","data":{"timestamp":" 946946525946"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946526160","data":{"timestamp":" 946946526160"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946526808","data":{"timestamp":" 946946526808"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKAA"," userResponse":" KUKAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946529457","data":{"timestamp":" 946946529455"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946530305","data":{"timestamp":" 946946530305"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946530566","data":{"timestamp":" 946946530565"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946531173","data":{"timestamp":" 946946531173"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946531813","data":{"timestamp":" 946946531812"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946533510","data":{"timestamp":" 946946533510"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWATAYARISHA"," userResponse":" WALIWATAYARISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946533707","data":{"timestamp":" 946946533707"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946534336","data":{"timestamp":" 946946534336"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946534711","data":{"timestamp":" 946946534710"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946535089","data":{"timestamp":" 946946535089"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946538769","data":{"timestamp":" 946946538769"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPENYEZA"," userResponse":" NILIPENYEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946539313","data":{"timestamp":" 946946539312"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946540107","data":{"timestamp":" 946946540107"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKAKAA"," userResponse":" NIKAKAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946540659","data":{"timestamp":" 946946540659"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946540833","data":{"timestamp":" 946946540833"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946541509","data":{"timestamp":" 946946541509"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHA"," userResponse":" DIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946543733","data":{"timestamp":" 946946543733"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946544570","data":{"timestamp":" 946946544569"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKETI"," userResponse":" ALIYEKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946545107","data":{"timestamp":" 946946545105"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946545705","data":{"timestamp":" 946946545705"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946546597","data":{"timestamp":" 946946546597"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHIKA"," userResponse":" ALISHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946547143","data":{"timestamp":" 946946547142"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946547408","data":{"timestamp":" 946946547408"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946548309","data":{"timestamp":" 946946548309"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PLASTIKI"," userResponse":" PLASTIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946548727","data":{"timestamp":" 946946548727"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946549356","data":{"timestamp":" 946946549356"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946550054","data":{"timestamp":" 946946550054"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946552501","data":{"timestamp":" 946946552501"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVAA"," userResponse":" ALIVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946553492","data":{"timestamp":" 946946553491"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946554452","data":{"timestamp":" 946946554452"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOZEEKA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOZEEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946555263","data":{"timestamp":" 946946555263"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOTI"," userResponse":" KOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946555882","data":{"timestamp":" 946946555882"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUKUU"," userResponse":" KUUKUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946556630","data":{"timestamp":" 946946556630"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946557705","data":{"timestamp":" 946946557705"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONEKANA"," userResponse":" ALIONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946558111","data":{"timestamp":" 946946558110"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946558397","data":{"timestamp":" 946946558397"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946559170","data":{"timestamp":" 946946559170"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIWASI"," userResponse":" WASIWASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946562607","data":{"timestamp":" 946946562607"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANGALIA"," userResponse":" NILIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946563253","data":{"timestamp":" 946946563253"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946563707","data":{"timestamp":" 946946563707"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946564509","data":{"timestamp":" 946946564509"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAMBUA"," userResponse":" KUTAMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946565231","data":{"timestamp":" 946946565230"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946566307","data":{"timestamp":" 946946566307"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946567200","data":{"timestamp":" 946946567200"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAONDOKA"," userResponse":" NAONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946568075","data":{"timestamp":" 946946568075"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946568849","data":{"timestamp":" 946946568849"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGU"," userResponse":" MWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946569638","data":{"timestamp":" 946946569638"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946570285","data":{"timestamp":" 946946570284"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAPO"," userResponse":" AMBAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946571367","data":{"timestamp":" 946946571366"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILILELEWA"," userResponse":" NILILELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946574002","data":{"timestamp":" 946946574002"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946574636","data":{"timestamp":" 946946574636"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAENDA"," userResponse":" NAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946575250","data":{"timestamp":" 946946575250"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946575693","data":{"timestamp":" 946946575693"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946576277","data":{"timestamp":" 946946576277"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946579702","data":{"timestamp":" 946946579701"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPAKIAJI"," userResponse":" UPAKIAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946580345","data":{"timestamp":" 946946580345"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946581809","data":{"timestamp":" 946946581809"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAMILIKA"," userResponse":" ULIKAMILIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946582404","data":{"timestamp":" 946946582403"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946583066","data":{"timestamp":" 946946583066"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946583671","data":{"timestamp":" 946946583671"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAWA"," userResponse":" WAKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946584594","data":{"timestamp":" 946946584594"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEKETI"," userResponse":" WAMEKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946587393","data":{"timestamp":" 946946587392"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHUUZI"," userResponse":" WACHUUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946588276","data":{"timestamp":" 946946588276"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIZIDI"," userResponse":" WALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946589520","data":{"timestamp":" 946946589520"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSUKUMANA"," userResponse":" KUSUKUMANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946590545","data":{"timestamp":" 946946590544"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAKA"," userResponse":" KUTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946591309","data":{"timestamp":" 946946591309"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUINGIA"," userResponse":" KUINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946591914","data":{"timestamp":" 946946591914"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946592070","data":{"timestamp":" 946946592070"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946592666","data":{"timestamp":" 946946592666"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946593394","data":{"timestamp":" 946946593393"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946593902","data":{"timestamp":" 946946593902"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAUZE"," userResponse":" WAUZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946594510","data":{"timestamp":" 946946594509"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDHAA"," userResponse":" BIDHAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946595005","data":{"timestamp":" 946946595005"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946597260","data":{"timestamp":" 946946597260"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946598036","data":{"timestamp":" 946946598036"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946599157","data":{"timestamp":" 946946599157"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAJA"," userResponse":" ALITAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946599368","data":{"timestamp":" 946946599368"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946600161","data":{"timestamp":" 946946600161"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946601928","data":{"timestamp":" 946946601928"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJINA"," userResponse":" MAJINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946602252","data":{"timestamp":" 946946602251"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946602857","data":{"timestamp":" 946946602857"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDHAA"," userResponse":" BIDHAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946603852","data":{"timestamp":" 946946603852"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIVYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946604626","data":{"timestamp":" 946946604626"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAUZA"," userResponse":" ANAUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946607247","data":{"timestamp":" 946946607247"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maneno yao yalinifurahisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANENO"," userResponse":" MANENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946607675","data":{"timestamp":" 946946607675"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maneno yao yalinifurahisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946609053","data":{"timestamp":" 946946609053"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maneno yao yalinifurahisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALINIFURAHISHA"," userResponse":" YALINIFURAHISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946612089","data":{"timestamp":" 946946612089"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946612254","data":{"timestamp":" 946946612253"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946613049","data":{"timestamp":" 946946613049"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946614377","data":{"timestamp":" 946946614377"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALINUNUA"," userResponse":" WALINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946615188","data":{"timestamp":" 946946615187"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINYWAJI"," userResponse":" VINYWAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946617760","data":{"timestamp":" 946946617760"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946618759","data":{"timestamp":" 946946618759"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKANUNUA"," userResponse":" WAKANUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946619911","data":{"timestamp":" 946946619910"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAFUNAJI"," userResponse":" VITAFUNAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946620712","data":{"timestamp":" 946946620712"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946621151","data":{"timestamp":" 946946621151"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946621754","data":{"timestamp":" 946946621754"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946622661","data":{"timestamp":" 946946622661"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUNA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946625408","data":{"timestamp":" 946946625407"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WASIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946625627","data":{"timestamp":" 946946625627"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946626200","data":{"timestamp":" 946946626200"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FEDHA"," userResponse":" FEDHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946626888","data":{"timestamp":" 946946626887"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946627550","data":{"timestamp":" 946946627549"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946628665","data":{"timestamp":" 946946628664"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAZAMA"," userResponse":" WALITAZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946629068","data":{"timestamp":" 946946629068"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946632285","data":{"timestamp":" 946946632284"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" SHUGHULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946632626","data":{"timestamp":" 946946632626"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946633658","data":{"timestamp":" 946946633658"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKATIZWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKATIZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946633887","data":{"timestamp":" 946946633887"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946634353","data":{"timestamp":" 946946634353"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIO"," userResponse":" MLIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946634688","data":{"timestamp":" 946946634688"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946635295","data":{"timestamp":" 946946635295"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HONI"," userResponse":" HONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946635797","data":{"timestamp":" 946946635796"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946636351","data":{"timestamp":" 946946636351"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946637232","data":{"timestamp":" 946946637231"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISHARA"," userResponse":" ISHARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946637856","data":{"timestamp":" 946946637855"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946638830","data":{"timestamp":" 946946638830"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946639701","data":{"timestamp":" 946946639700"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946640586","data":{"timestamp":" 946946640586"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONDOKA"," userResponse":" KUONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946643326","data":{"timestamp":" 946946643325"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" KONDAKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946644242","data":{"timestamp":" 946946644240"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWATAKA"," userResponse":" ALIWATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946645055","data":{"timestamp":" 946946645054"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHUUZI"," userResponse":" WACHUUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946645857","data":{"timestamp":" 946946645856"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONDOKA"," userResponse":" KUONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946646387","data":{"timestamp":" 946946646387"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946646501","data":{"timestamp":" 946946646501"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946647021","data":{"timestamp":" 946946647021"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946650185","data":{"timestamp":" 946946650185"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHUUZI"," userResponse":" WACHUUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946651435","data":{"timestamp":" 946946651434"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISUKUMANA"," userResponse":" WALISUKUMANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946652130","data":{"timestamp":" 946946652129"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946653306","data":{"timestamp":" 946946653306"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" WAKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946653759","data":{"timestamp":" 946946653759"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946654012","data":{"timestamp":" 946946654012"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946654729","data":{"timestamp":" 946946654729"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHUKA"," userResponse":" KUSHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946657154","data":{"timestamp":" 946946657154"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946657799","data":{"timestamp":" 946946657799"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946659252","data":{"timestamp":" 946946659252"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWARUDISHA"," userResponse":" WALIWARUDISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946660007","data":{"timestamp":" 946946660005"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946660861","data":{"timestamp":" 946946660861"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASALIO"," userResponse":" MASALIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946661113","data":{"timestamp":" 946946661113"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946661559","data":{"timestamp":" 946946661558"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELA"," userResponse":" HELA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946662059","data":{"timestamp":" 946946662058"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946664488","data":{"timestamp":" 946946664488"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946665302","data":{"timestamp":" 946946665302"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946665962","data":{"timestamp":" 946946665961"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUHUDI"," userResponse":" JUHUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946666205","data":{"timestamp":" 946946666205"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946666852","data":{"timestamp":" 946946666852"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946667666","data":{"timestamp":" 946946667665"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUZA"," userResponse":" KUUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946668258","data":{"timestamp":" 946946668257"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDHAA"," userResponse":" BIDHAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946668730","data":{"timestamp":" 946946668729"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946671745","data":{"timestamp":" 946946671744"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946673077","data":{"timestamp":" 946946673077"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" LILIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946674068","data":{"timestamp":" 946946674068"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUONI"," userResponse":" KITUONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946675475","data":{"timestamp":" 946946675475"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILICHUNGULIA"," userResponse":" NILICHUNGULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946676303","data":{"timestamp":" 946946676302"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHANI"," userResponse":" DIRISHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946679381","data":{"timestamp":" 946946679381"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" NILIJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946679978","data":{"timestamp":" 946946679977"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946680783","data":{"timestamp":" 946946680783"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEWAHI"," userResponse":" NINGEWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946681404","data":{"timestamp":" 946946681404"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946682216","data":{"timestamp":" 946946682216"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946682688","data":{"timestamp":" 946946682687"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGU"," userResponse":" MWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946683285","data":{"timestamp":" 946946683285"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946686703","data":{"timestamp":" 946946686702"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946688043","data":{"timestamp":" 946946688043"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOENDELEA"," userResponse":" ILIPOENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946689024","data":{"timestamp":" 946946689024"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946689768","data":{"timestamp":" 946946689768"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946690605","data":{"timestamp":" 946946690605"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINGI"," userResponse":" JINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946691114","data":{"timestamp":" 946946691114"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946691229","data":{"timestamp":" 946946691229"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946691806","data":{"timestamp":" 946946691806"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946694623","data":{"timestamp":" 946946694622"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIYAFUMBA"," userResponse":" NILIYAFUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946695110","data":{"timestamp":" 946946695110"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946695587","data":{"timestamp":" 946946695587"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946696880","data":{"timestamp":" 946946696880"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKINUIA"," userResponse":" NIKINUIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946697555","data":{"timestamp":" 946946697554"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946700802","data":{"timestamp":" 946946700802"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946701407","data":{"timestamp":" 946946701407"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWAZO"," userResponse":" MAWAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946701922","data":{"timestamp":" 946946701922"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946702977","data":{"timestamp":" 946946702977"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIREJEA"," userResponse":" YALIREJEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946703882","data":{"timestamp":" 946946703882"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946706117","data":{"timestamp":" 946946706116"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946707302","data":{"timestamp":" 946946707302"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946708117","data":{"timestamp":" 946946708117"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKUWA"," userResponse":" ATAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946709250","data":{"timestamp":" 946946709250"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SALAMA"," userResponse":" SALAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946711614","data":{"timestamp":" 946946711614"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946712490","data":{"timestamp":" 946946712490"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946713234","data":{"timestamp":" 946946713234"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946714260","data":{"timestamp":" 946946714260"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATALETA"," userResponse":" WATALETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946714692","data":{"timestamp":" 946946714692"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELA"," userResponse":" HELA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946715538","data":{"timestamp":" 946946715538"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946717650","data":{"timestamp":" 946946717650"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946718579","data":{"timestamp":" 946946718579"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946719014","data":{"timestamp":" 946946719014"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946720133","data":{"timestamp":" 946946720133"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" ATAKUMBUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946721259","data":{"timestamp":" 946946721258"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYUNYIZIA"," userResponse":" KUNYUNYIZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946721725","data":{"timestamp":" 946946721725"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946722376","data":{"timestamp":" 946946722376"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MICHE"," userResponse":" MICHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946722443","data":{"timestamp":" 946946722443"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946722965","data":{"timestamp":" 946946722965"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946723533","data":{"timestamp":" 946946723533"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946726949","data":{"timestamp":" 946946726949"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946727946","data":{"timestamp":" 946946727946"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKARIRI"," userResponse":" NILIKARIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946728795","data":{"timestamp":" 946946728794"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946729072","data":{"timestamp":" 946946729071"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946731619","data":{"timestamp":" 946946731619"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946732508","data":{"timestamp":" 946946732507"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBANGU"," userResponse":" MJOMBANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946733273","data":{"timestamp":" 946946733273"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946734217","data":{"timestamp":" 946946734217"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946734662","data":{"timestamp":" 946946734662"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946735203","data":{"timestamp":" 946946735203"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946738000","data":{"timestamp":" 946946738000"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946738455","data":{"timestamp":" 946946738455"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946739894","data":{"timestamp":" 946946739894"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJISEMEA"," userResponse":" NAJISEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946740544","data":{"timestamp":" 946946740543"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946741354","data":{"timestamp":" 946946741354"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPATWA"," userResponse":" NILIPATWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946741550","data":{"timestamp":" 946946741550"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946742351","data":{"timestamp":" 946946742351"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" USINGIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946744977","data":{"timestamp":" 946946744977"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946745216","data":{"timestamp":" 946946745216"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946745550","data":{"timestamp":" 946946745550"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946746145","data":{"timestamp":" 946946746145"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946747359","data":{"timestamp":" 946946747358"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIAMSHWA"," userResponse":" NILIAMSHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946747625","data":{"timestamp":" 946946747625"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946748423","data":{"timestamp":" 946946748423"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946748632","data":{"timestamp":" 946946748632"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946749356","data":{"timestamp":" 946946749356"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUITA"," userResponse":" KUITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946750126","data":{"timestamp":" 946946750126"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946751294","data":{"timestamp":" 946946751294"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKWENDA"," userResponse":" WALIOKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946751914","data":{"timestamp":" 946946751913"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946752549","data":{"timestamp":" 946946752548"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946753125","data":{"timestamp":" 946946753125"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946755810","data":{"timestamp":" 946946755810"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" NILICHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946756297","data":{"timestamp":" 946946756296"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946756736","data":{"timestamp":" 946946756735"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946757525","data":{"timestamp":" 946946757524"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946757946","data":{"timestamp":" 946946757946"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946758801","data":{"timestamp":" 946946758801"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946759364","data":{"timestamp":" 946946759363"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946759440","data":{"timestamp":" 946946759440"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946759893","data":{"timestamp":" 946946759893"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946762874","data":{"timestamp":" 946946762874"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946762969","data":{"timestamp":" 946946762969"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946763843","data":{"timestamp":" 946946763843"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946764746","data":{"timestamp":" 946946764745"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946765601","data":{"timestamp":" 946946765601"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAJAA"," userResponse":" LINAJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946766195","data":{"timestamp":" 946946766195"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPESI"," userResponse":" UPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946768450","data":{"timestamp":" 946946768449"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946769069","data":{"timestamp":" 946946769069"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946769720","data":{"timestamp":" 946946769719"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946770617","data":{"timestamp":" 946946770617"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGEANZA"," userResponse":" LINGEANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946771625","data":{"timestamp":" 946946771625"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946771728","data":{"timestamp":" 946946771728"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946772184","data":{"timestamp":" 946946772184"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946773124","data":{"timestamp":" 946946773124"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHARIKI"," userResponse":" MASHARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946775514","data":{"timestamp":" 946946775514"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946775657","data":{"timestamp":" 946946775656"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946776927","data":{"timestamp":" 946946776927"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAANA"," userResponse":" MAANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946777444","data":{"timestamp":" 946946777444"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946778125","data":{"timestamp":" 946946778125"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946778958","data":{"timestamp":" 946946778958"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946779523","data":{"timestamp":" 946946779523"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946780168","data":{"timestamp":" 946946780168"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946781054","data":{"timestamp":" 946946781054"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946781879","data":{"timestamp":" 946946781879"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946782124","data":{"timestamp":" 946946782123"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946783025","data":{"timestamp":" 946946783024"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBANGU"," userResponse":" MJOMBANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946785227","data":{"timestamp":" 946946785226"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946785330","data":{"timestamp":" 946946785330"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" eaf8a2ae-8c99-4ac6-b010-65897c22793f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBANGU"," userResponse":" MJOMBANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946801180","data":{"timestamp":" 946946801180"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 5b6c1882-acad-4d82-95b1-1b43ba64bc5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946805563","data":{"timestamp":" 946946805563"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 5b6c1882-acad-4d82-95b1-1b43ba64bc5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946810005","data":{"timestamp":" 946946810005"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 5b6c1882-acad-4d82-95b1-1b43ba64bc5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946815129","data":{"timestamp":" 946946815129"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 5b6c1882-acad-4d82-95b1-1b43ba64bc5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946820270","data":{"timestamp":" 946946820270"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 5b6c1882-acad-4d82-95b1-1b43ba64bc5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946824842","data":{"timestamp":" 946946824842"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 5b6c1882-acad-4d82-95b1-1b43ba64bc5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946833548","data":{"timestamp":" 946946833548"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 5b6c1882-acad-4d82-95b1-1b43ba64bc5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946841099","data":{"timestamp":" 946946841099"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 5b6c1882-acad-4d82-95b1-1b43ba64bc5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946847977","data":{"timestamp":" 946946847976"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 5b6c1882-acad-4d82-95b1-1b43ba64bc5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946852414","data":{"timestamp":" 946946852413"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 5b6c1882-acad-4d82-95b1-1b43ba64bc5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946856807","data":{"timestamp":" 946946856807"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 5b6c1882-acad-4d82-95b1-1b43ba64bc5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946862648","data":{"timestamp":" 946946862647"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 5b6c1882-acad-4d82-95b1-1b43ba64bc5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946882480","data":{"timestamp":" 946946882480"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 32cd9cf9-6521-462d-b4e1-fac83c73d466"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-9-11"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946897308","data":{"timestamp":" 946946897308"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 32cd9cf9-6521-462d-b4e1-fac83c73d466"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-9-11"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946907156","data":{"timestamp":" 946946907156"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 32cd9cf9-6521-462d-b4e1-fac83c73d466"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-9-11"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946912640","data":{"timestamp":" 946946912639"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 32cd9cf9-6521-462d-b4e1-fac83c73d466"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-10-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946921727","data":{"timestamp":" 946946921727"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 32cd9cf9-6521-462d-b4e1-fac83c73d466"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-10-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946928725","data":{"timestamp":" 946946928724"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 32cd9cf9-6521-462d-b4e1-fac83c73d466"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-13"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946935853","data":{"timestamp":" 946946935853"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 32cd9cf9-6521-462d-b4e1-fac83c73d466"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-12-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946943181","data":{"timestamp":" 946946943181"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 32cd9cf9-6521-462d-b4e1-fac83c73d466"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946953515","data":{"timestamp":" 946946953515"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 32cd9cf9-6521-462d-b4e1-fac83c73d466"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946966182","data":{"timestamp":" 946946966182"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 32cd9cf9-6521-462d-b4e1-fac83c73d466"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946972292","data":{"timestamp":" 946946972291"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 32cd9cf9-6521-462d-b4e1-fac83c73d466"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946978022","data":{"timestamp":" 946946978022"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 32cd9cf9-6521-462d-b4e1-fac83c73d466"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946984551","data":{"timestamp":" 946946984551"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 32cd9cf9-6521-462d-b4e1-fac83c73d466"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-2-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946993205","data":{"timestamp":" 946946993205"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 32cd9cf9-6521-462d-b4e1-fac83c73d466"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946998258","data":{"timestamp":" 946946998257"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 32cd9cf9-6521-462d-b4e1-fac83c73d466"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_8-1-10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947006149","data":{"timestamp":" 946947006148"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 32cd9cf9-6521-462d-b4e1-fac83c73d466"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_1_8-1-10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947024795","data":{"timestamp":" 946947024794"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 42b2318a-f773-4c58-b6a8-a6b250e02b9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947025185","data":{"timestamp":" 946947025184"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 42b2318a-f773-4c58-b6a8-a6b250e02b9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947025419","data":{"timestamp":" 946947025418"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 42b2318a-f773-4c58-b6a8-a6b250e02b9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947025746","data":{"timestamp":" 946947025746"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 42b2318a-f773-4c58-b6a8-a6b250e02b9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947025990","data":{"timestamp":" 946947025989"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 42b2318a-f773-4c58-b6a8-a6b250e02b9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947035558","data":{"timestamp":" 946947035557"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 42b2318a-f773-4c58-b6a8-a6b250e02b9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947035667","data":{"timestamp":" 946947035667"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 42b2318a-f773-4c58-b6a8-a6b250e02b9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947053305","data":{"timestamp":" 946947053305"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947054142","data":{"timestamp":" 946947054141"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947054872","data":{"timestamp":" 946947054871"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947055111","data":{"timestamp":" 946947055110"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947055679","data":{"timestamp":" 946947055678"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947056484","data":{"timestamp":" 946947056484"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVIVU"," userResponse":" MVIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947056858","data":{"timestamp":" 946947056858"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947057522","data":{"timestamp":" 946947057522"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINGA"," userResponse":" MJINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947060031","data":{"timestamp":" 946947060031"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947060225","data":{"timestamp":" 946947060225"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947060869","data":{"timestamp":" 946947060869"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947061515","data":{"timestamp":" 946947061514"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947062150","data":{"timestamp":" 946947062150"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947062755","data":{"timestamp":" 946947062754"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKA"," userResponse":" KICHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947062970","data":{"timestamp":" 946947062970"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947063866","data":{"timestamp":" 946947063866"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAHARI"," userResponse":" KALAHARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947067112","data":{"timestamp":" 946947067112"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947067726","data":{"timestamp":" 946947067726"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947068511","data":{"timestamp":" 946947068511"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947069136","data":{"timestamp":" 946947069136"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947070152","data":{"timestamp":" 946947070152"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMKA"," userResponse":" ALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947070656","data":{"timestamp":" 946947070655"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947071512","data":{"timestamp":" 946947071512"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPATA"," userResponse":" KUMPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947072287","data":{"timestamp":" 946947072287"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947073015","data":{"timestamp":" 946947073014"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947073771","data":{"timestamp":" 946947073771"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUANI"," userResponse":" JUANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947076267","data":{"timestamp":" 946947076267"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947077146","data":{"timestamp":" 946947077145"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947078009","data":{"timestamp":" 946947078009"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947078384","data":{"timestamp":" 946947078384"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947078882","data":{"timestamp":" 946947078882"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947079595","data":{"timestamp":" 946947079595"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947080030","data":{"timestamp":" 946947080030"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947080809","data":{"timestamp":" 946947080808"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZINI"," userResponse":" ZIZINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947083127","data":{"timestamp":" 946947083127"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947083889","data":{"timestamp":" 946947083889"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANA"," userResponse":" KIJANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947084437","data":{"timestamp":" 946947084437"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947084943","data":{"timestamp":" 946947084943"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVIVU"," userResponse":" MVIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947085452","data":{"timestamp":" 946947085452"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947087850","data":{"timestamp":" 946947087850"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENDA"," userResponse":" NENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947088965","data":{"timestamp":" 946947088965"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAMTAFUTE"," userResponse":" UKAMTAFUTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947089288","data":{"timestamp":" 946947089288"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947092227","data":{"timestamp":" 946947092227"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEZEEKA"," userResponse":" NIMEZEEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947092772","data":{"timestamp":" 946947092772"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947093402","data":{"timestamp":" 946947093402"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIWEZI"," userResponse":" SIWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947094335","data":{"timestamp":" 946947094335"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUKIMU"," userResponse":" KUKUKIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947094786","data":{"timestamp":" 946947094786"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947095967","data":{"timestamp":" 946947095966"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947096429","data":{"timestamp":" 946947096429"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947097280","data":{"timestamp":" 946947097280"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947099256","data":{"timestamp":" 946947099256"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947099969","data":{"timestamp":" 946947099969"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947100615","data":{"timestamp":" 946947100614"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947101425","data":{"timestamp":" 946947101425"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" ALIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947102010","data":{"timestamp":" 946947102010"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947102202","data":{"timestamp":" 946947102201"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947103132","data":{"timestamp":" 946947103132"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947103567","data":{"timestamp":" 946947103567"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947104441","data":{"timestamp":" 946947104441"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALISHONI"," userResponse":" MALISHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947116155","data":{"timestamp":" 946947116155"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" KICHAKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947117035","data":{"timestamp":" 946947117035"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947117513","data":{"timestamp":" 946947117513"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947118759","data":{"timestamp":" 946947118759"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOANGAZA"," userResponse":" KILICHOANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947119305","data":{"timestamp":" 946947119305"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947119452","data":{"timestamp":" 946947119452"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947119986","data":{"timestamp":" 946947119986"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAMBA"," userResponse":" MWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947122840","data":{"timestamp":" 946947122840"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alizidi kuukaribia mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947123955","data":{"timestamp":" 946947123955"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alizidi kuukaribia mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUKARIBIA"," userResponse":" KUUKARIBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947124503","data":{"timestamp":" 946947124503"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alizidi kuukaribia mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAMBA"," userResponse":" MWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947127245","data":{"timestamp":" 946947127244"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIPOZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947128474","data":{"timestamp":" 946947128473"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUKARIBIA"," userResponse":" KUUKARIBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947129236","data":{"timestamp":" 946947129236"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIPO"," userResponse":" NDIPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947129915","data":{"timestamp":" 946947129915"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGAZA"," userResponse":" MWANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947130741","data":{"timestamp":" 946947130740"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" ULIPOZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947131585","data":{"timestamp":" 946947131584"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENDEZA"," userResponse":" KUPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947134047","data":{"timestamp":" 946947134047"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947134537","data":{"timestamp":" 946947134537"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947135057","data":{"timestamp":" 946947135057"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYE"," userResponse":" NDIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947135559","data":{"timestamp":" 946947135559"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947136203","data":{"timestamp":" 946947136203"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947139559","data":{"timestamp":" 946947139558"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947139569","data":{"timestamp":" 946947139568"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947140059","data":{"timestamp":" 946947140059"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947140826","data":{"timestamp":" 946947140826"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947141791","data":{"timestamp":" 946947141790"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUELEZA"," userResponse":" ALIUELEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947142438","data":{"timestamp":" 946947142438"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNG"," userResponse":" MNG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947142444","data":{"timestamp":" 946947142444"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARO"," userResponse":" ARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947145159","data":{"timestamp":" 946947145159"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947145492","data":{"timestamp":" 946947145492"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947145675","data":{"timestamp":" 946947145675"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947146559","data":{"timestamp":" 946947146559"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947148935","data":{"timestamp":" 946947148934"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBONA"," userResponse":" MBONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947149188","data":{"timestamp":" 946947149188"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKO"," userResponse":" UKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947150057","data":{"timestamp":" 946947150056"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947150562","data":{"timestamp":" 946947150562"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947152858","data":{"timestamp":" 946947152858"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947153092","data":{"timestamp":" 946947153092"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947153530","data":{"timestamp":" 946947153529"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947154196","data":{"timestamp":" 946947154196"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNG"," userResponse":" MNG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947154206","data":{"timestamp":" 946947154206"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARO"," userResponse":" ARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947155039","data":{"timestamp":" 946947155038"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIJIBU"," userResponse":" ULIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947157540","data":{"timestamp":" 946947157540"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947158161","data":{"timestamp":" 946947158161"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947159387","data":{"timestamp":" 946947159387"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALINIACHA"," userResponse":" WALINIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947159932","data":{"timestamp":" 946947159932"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947160788","data":{"timestamp":" 946947160787"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947161596","data":{"timestamp":" 946947161596"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHAMA"," userResponse":" WALIHAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947172995","data":{"timestamp":" 946947172995"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUTAKA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947175653","data":{"timestamp":" 946947175653"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIBEBA"," userResponse":" KUNIBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947178605","data":{"timestamp":" 946947178605"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAANAKE"," userResponse":" MAANAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947179021","data":{"timestamp":" 946947179021"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947179195","data":{"timestamp":" 946947179195"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947179632","data":{"timestamp":" 946947179631"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947180135","data":{"timestamp":" 946947180135"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947183973","data":{"timestamp":" 946947183972"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947184806","data":{"timestamp":" 946947184806"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947185592","data":{"timestamp":" 946947185591"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947185985","data":{"timestamp":" 946947185985"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947186861","data":{"timestamp":" 946947186861"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947186876","data":{"timestamp":" 946947186876"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947187661","data":{"timestamp":" 946947187661"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947190007","data":{"timestamp":" 946947190007"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947191052","data":{"timestamp":" 946947191052"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUBEBA"," userResponse":" NITAKUBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947194191","data":{"timestamp":" 946947194191"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUPELEKA"," userResponse":" NITAKUPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947195079","data":{"timestamp":" 946947195079"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947196054","data":{"timestamp":" 946947196054"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKUJULISHE"," userResponse":" NIKUJULISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947196359","data":{"timestamp":" 946947196359"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947197115","data":{"timestamp":" 946947197115"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947199729","data":{"timestamp":" 946947199729"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947200570","data":{"timestamp":" 946947200569"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAWEZA"," userResponse":" UNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947201355","data":{"timestamp":" 946947201355"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIBEBA"," userResponse":" NIBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947204198","data":{"timestamp":" 946947204198"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947205437","data":{"timestamp":" 946947205437"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USILALAMIKE"," userResponse":" USILALAMIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947205943","data":{"timestamp":" 946947205942"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIWA"," userResponse":" NIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947206249","data":{"timestamp":" 946947206249"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947206959","data":{"timestamp":" 946947206958"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947207813","data":{"timestamp":" 946947207813"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAVYOWEZA"," userResponse":" UNAVYOWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947208741","data":{"timestamp":" 946947208741"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHIMILI"," userResponse":" KUHIMILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947209397","data":{"timestamp":" 946947209397"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947217587","data":{"timestamp":" 946947217586"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILISEMA"," userResponse":" LILISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947222739","data":{"timestamp":" 946947222739"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947229473","data":{"timestamp":" 946947229473"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947230189","data":{"timestamp":" 946947230189"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947230808","data":{"timestamp":" 946947230807"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" ALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947231485","data":{"timestamp":" 946947231485"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947231860","data":{"timestamp":" 946947231860"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947232488","data":{"timestamp":" 946947232488"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947233098","data":{"timestamp":" 946947233098"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947233699","data":{"timestamp":" 946947233699"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947234637","data":{"timestamp":" 946947234636"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" MGONGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947242479","data":{"timestamp":" 946947242479"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947242935","data":{"timestamp":" 946947242934"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947243621","data":{"timestamp":" 946947243621"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947243726","data":{"timestamp":" 946947243726"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947261036","data":{"timestamp":" 946947261036"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947261860","data":{"timestamp":" 946947261860"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUGUZA"," userResponse":" ALIUGUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947262414","data":{"timestamp":" 946947262414"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGO"," userResponse":" MGONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947262610","data":{"timestamp":" 946947262610"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947263084","data":{"timestamp":" 946947263084"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947263609","data":{"timestamp":" 946947263609"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947264304","data":{"timestamp":" 946947264304"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947264883","data":{"timestamp":" 946947264883"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" MAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947265638","data":{"timestamp":" 946947265638"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAALUMU"," userResponse":" MAALUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947267655","data":{"timestamp":" 946947267655"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947268339","data":{"timestamp":" 946947268339"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947269062","data":{"timestamp":" 946947269062"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAMEA"," userResponse":" YAKAMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947269437","data":{"timestamp":" 946947269437"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947270120","data":{"timestamp":" 946947270120"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947272765","data":{"timestamp":" 946947272765"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947273440","data":{"timestamp":" 946947273440"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947274156","data":{"timestamp":" 946947274156"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947274773","data":{"timestamp":" 946947274773"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" ALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947275448","data":{"timestamp":" 946947275447"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947275822","data":{"timestamp":" 946947275822"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947276446","data":{"timestamp":" 946947276446"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947277020","data":{"timestamp":" 946947277020"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947277596","data":{"timestamp":" 946947277596"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947278531","data":{"timestamp":" 946947278531"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" MGONGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947279189","data":{"timestamp":" 946947279189"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947279647","data":{"timestamp":" 946947279646"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947280332","data":{"timestamp":" 946947280332"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947280758","data":{"timestamp":" 946947280758"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947283496","data":{"timestamp":" 946947283496"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947284321","data":{"timestamp":" 946947284320"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUGUZA"," userResponse":" ALIUGUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947284877","data":{"timestamp":" 946947284877"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGO"," userResponse":" MGONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947285155","data":{"timestamp":" 946947285155"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947285631","data":{"timestamp":" 946947285630"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947286155","data":{"timestamp":" 946947286155"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947286851","data":{"timestamp":" 946947286851"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947287426","data":{"timestamp":" 946947287425"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" MAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947288181","data":{"timestamp":" 946947288181"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAALUMU"," userResponse":" MAALUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947290639","data":{"timestamp":" 946947290639"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947291323","data":{"timestamp":" 946947291322"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947292048","data":{"timestamp":" 946947292048"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAMEA"," userResponse":" YAKAMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947292421","data":{"timestamp":" 946947292421"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947293104","data":{"timestamp":" 946947293104"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947296497","data":{"timestamp":" 946947296497"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947297102","data":{"timestamp":" 946947297101"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947297636","data":{"timestamp":" 946947297636"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPYA"," userResponse":" MAPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947298322","data":{"timestamp":" 946947298322"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947298737","data":{"timestamp":" 946947298737"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947299484","data":{"timestamp":" 946947299484"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947299669","data":{"timestamp":" 946947299668"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947300022","data":{"timestamp":" 946947300022"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947300618","data":{"timestamp":" 946947300617"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGINE"," userResponse":" MENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947301422","data":{"timestamp":" 946947301422"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILINI"," userResponse":" MWILINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947303740","data":{"timestamp":" 946947303740"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947304293","data":{"timestamp":" 946947304293"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947305088","data":{"timestamp":" 946947305088"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947306173","data":{"timestamp":" 946947306173"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIMKUMBUSHA"," userResponse":" ZILIMKUMBUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947306719","data":{"timestamp":" 946947306718"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947307402","data":{"timestamp":" 946947307402"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947307979","data":{"timestamp":" 946947307979"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947309033","data":{"timestamp":" 946947309033"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKUWA"," userResponse":" KUTOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947309740","data":{"timestamp":" 946947309740"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINGA"," userResponse":" MJINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947310235","data":{"timestamp":" 946947310235"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947339981","data":{"timestamp":" 946947339980"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947340096","data":{"timestamp":" 946947340096"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 027cf713-52d0-4008-8a87-93dd84b23c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947360673","data":{"timestamp":" 946947360673"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 6e2c034a-a999-4985-a2ee-9bbbeb6a5e25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mfa_vu_nzi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947367349","data":{"timestamp":" 946947367349"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 6e2c034a-a999-4985-a2ee-9bbbeb6a5e25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_gha_vu_mba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947374034","data":{"timestamp":" 946947374034"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 6e2c034a-a999-4985-a2ee-9bbbeb6a5e25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_wa_vu_nchi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947380715","data":{"timestamp":" 946947380714"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 6e2c034a-a999-4985-a2ee-9bbbeb6a5e25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vu_ye_ngu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947387446","data":{"timestamp":" 946947387445"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 6e2c034a-a999-4985-a2ee-9bbbeb6a5e25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vu_nji_mwe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947394134","data":{"timestamp":" 946947394133"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 6e2c034a-a999-4985-a2ee-9bbbeb6a5e25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mu_fu_vu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947400839","data":{"timestamp":" 946947400839"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 6e2c034a-a999-4985-a2ee-9bbbeb6a5e25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mle_vu_vyi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947407534","data":{"timestamp":" 946947407533"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 6e2c034a-a999-4985-a2ee-9bbbeb6a5e25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pi_vyi_vu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947414214","data":{"timestamp":" 946947414214"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 6e2c034a-a999-4985-a2ee-9bbbeb6a5e25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vu_shu_vya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947420924","data":{"timestamp":" 946947420924"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 6e2c034a-a999-4985-a2ee-9bbbeb6a5e25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ze_mbu_vu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947434118","data":{"timestamp":" 946947434117"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_181429"," gameId":" 6e2c034a-a999-4985-a2ee-9bbbeb6a5e25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_ze_mbu_vu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}